{
    "id": "8edc2aff7b48423bb37fc51184b322ec",
    "title": "Degrees of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am the ……………….. student in my class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "youngest",
                "younger",
                "young"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cae734d1c22b4703b2dcba774cbf7e01"
        },
        {
            "question": "This has been the …………….. summer we have ever had.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "worse",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a7dba2d8f3646188fc8e41c14379ed6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani is a ……………….. girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettier",
                "prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c962a21d775c49b189dc08b3e98ee6d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "At one time, the Empire State building was the ……………….. building in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c2a0f9b6b23d4800917f8bf406aeb807"
        },
        {
            "question": "China is ………………. than India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "large",
                "larger",
                "largest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47a81f4da3644f8d9cb8c3418a8f2651"
        },
        {
            "question": "Diamond is …………….. than steel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "hardest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79e51ae951874819a65b3e8daef3c343"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pen is ……………… than the sword.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mighty",
                "mightier",
                "mightiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbf9223f412e4d1e8f9e1197d36bc159"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Taj Mahal is one of the ………………… buildings in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more beautiful",
                "most beautiful",
                "beautifulest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4219d2674254450bb7e7b912f5983197"
        },
        {
            "question": "An honest man is the ..................... work of God.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noble",
                "nobler",
                "noblest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "effde27921554a4d9e17036d1d7b3431"
        },
        {
            "question": "Patience is a ………………. virtue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "greater",
                "greatest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcee4eaaf0454e7c999dd1b2567e5491"
        }
    ]
}